var Questions = [];

var q1 = {
  question : "What is the other name of Mahabharata?",
  answer : "Jaya"
};

Questions.push(q1);

var q2 = {
  question : "Who was Sikhandi in her last birth?",
  answer : "Amba"
};

Questions.push(q2);

var q3 = {
  question : "Who was the surviving kid of the Pandavas?",
  answer : "Parikshit"
}

Questions.push(q3);

var q4 = {
  question : "Who was Kunti's first born?",
  answer : "Karna"
};

Questions.push(q4);

var q5 = {
  question : "How many days did the battle of Kurukshetra happen?",
  answer : "18"
};

Questions.push(q5);

var q6 = {
  question : "What was the birthplace of Lord Krishna?",
  answer : "Mathura"
};

Questions.push(q6);

var q7 = {
  question : "How many kids were Gandhari blessed with?",
  answer : "100"
};

Questions.push(q7);

var q8 = {
  question : "What did Bheeshma bestow to the Pandavas when he was on his deathbed?",
  answer : "Vishu Sahasranama"
};

Questions.push(q8);

var q9 = {
  question : "Whom did Eklavya worship as his Guru?",
  answer : "Drona"
};

Questions.push(q9);

var q10 = {
  question : "What animal followed Dharma to heaven?",
  answer : "Dog"
};

Questions.push(q10);

module.exports = Questions;